这个显然没用
Well,that thing's clearly in the way.
好吧
All right.
死冰箱
Damn fridge!
乔伊，你好吗？
-Hi,Joey. How you doing? -Great...
很好，室友
roomie.
我们现在的确是室友 没错，经你一提
-I guess we are roommates. -I know.Now that you bring it up,
我们的冰箱坏了，得买台新的
our fridge is broken.We need a new one.
我算过，你得出4百 感激不尽
I checked and your half is $400. Thanks a lot.
我才不跟你分 我只住到我们那边整理好为止
I'm not paying for that.I'm just here while they fix my place.
瑞秋，这台冰箱是我出生之后 我父母买的
Look,Rach,my parents bought this fridge just after I was born. Okay?
我用都没问题 你一来它就坏了
I have never had a problem with it. Then you show up and it breaks!
这意味着什么？
What does that tell you?
冰箱无法和人一样长寿
That refrigerators don't live as long as people?
好，你也知道自动提款机 一次只能提3百
You know the ATM only lets you take out 300,so...
剩下的1百我就收支票
I'll take a check for the rest.
你在开玩笑吧？
You're joking,right?
当然是开玩笑了，我不收支票
Of course I'm joking. I don't take checks.
幸好你很帅
Thank God,you're pretty.
本集播出：“乔伊的冰箱”
The One With Joey's Fridge
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
你们有认识的帅哥吗？
Hi! Do you guys know any cute guys?
当然有 就是我的好朋友乔伊
Of course. My good friend Joey over here.
我忘了…谢谢你钱德
I'm sorry. Thank you,Chandler.
周末有大型慈善晚会
There's a charity ball and Ralph Lauren has a table...
罗夫罗兰占了一桌，我也得去
so I have to go.
为什么筹款？ 不晓得
-What charity? -I don't know.
不是某种树就是某种病…
Something,either trees or disease...
罗夫很会唠叨
Ralph mumbles a lot.
罗夫都趁你不专心时唠叨吗
-He mumbles when you're not attentive?
对呀，好奇怪
-Yeah. It's weird.
总之我得找个男伴
But I need to find a date.
你想找什么样的人？
What kind of date?
自己有晚礼服或租得起晚礼服
Someone that has his own tux or the ability to rent a tux.
所以身家起码要有50元
So he has to be a male who has at least $50.
只差一点
So close.
大家好
-Hey,everybody! -Hi,there.
这是伊丽莎白
-This is Elizabeth. -Hi,Elizabeth.
我就是那个学生
I'm the student.
真可爱…才怪
Isn't she cute? Nope.
也许我不该多嘴 但你们在一起不是不能被看到吗
Weren't you guys supposed to...not be seen together?
我们没有在一起
We aren't.
没有，我们只是两个 在咖啡馆巧遇的人
We just happen to have run into each other here.
真奸诈
Oh,sly!
我很想多认识你们 但是我得走了
I wanted to meet you guys,but I have to run.
改天见 好
-See you later? -Okay.
罗斯再见 再见
-Bye,Ross. -Bye. See you.
老师，我不是故意撞到你的 没关系，女士
-Didn't mean to run into you,sir. -That's quite all right,ma'am.
她为什么要走？ 刚放学功课一大堆？
Why is she leaving? Is it a school night and she has homework?
对，她明天要交 分子流行病学报告
Yes. Her molecular epidemiology paper is due tomorrow.
帮我祝她好运
Tell her good luck with that.
还有吗？别客气
Anyone else? Bring them on.
她什么时候生日？
-When's her birthday?
我不知道，怎么了？
-I don't know. Why?
我好久没去“小鸡奶酪”吃儿童快餐了
It's just been so long since I've been to Chuck E. Cheese.
我喜欢伊丽莎白 谢谢
-I like Elizabeth. -Well,thanks.
我真的很喜欢她 叫她今年早点送童子军饼干来
I like her so much,tell her I want my cookies early this year.
我要薄荷巧克力饼和巧克力派
A box of Thin Mints and some Tagalongs.
你们别闹他了 说真的，你们交往得怎样？
Give him a break. Ross,how's it going with her?
非常好
It's been great.
她才20岁，还不想太认真 最适合现在的我
She's 20,so she's not too serious,which is perfect for me now.
太好了，她真的好像很不错
That's great. Seriously,she seems nice.
谢谢，我知道你们喜欢臭我 但我真的很希望你们能喜欢她
I know you guys like to give me a hard time...but it means a lot to me.
只要知道你们… 我想到一个很棒的
-Just knowing.. -Okay,I got a good one.
好，她是才12岁吗？
What is she,like,12?
钱德，你觉得我们的沟通够吗
Chandler,do we talk about our relationship enough?
够，有水果卷吗？
Yeah. Do we have any Fruit Roll-Ups?
我刚想到一个人 很适合当瑞秋的男伴
I thought of the perfect guy for Rachel to take to her thing.
有意思，我们也找到人了
That's so funny. We found someone too.
那好，她可以在我的人 和你们的怪胎之中选一个
Good. She'll have a choice between my guy and your weirdo.
为什么我们的人是怪胎？ 你们的品味就是那样
-Why would our guy be a weirdo? -Because that's just your taste.
瑞秋才不会选你的蠢人
See,Rachel's not gonna pick your stupid guy.
是吗？ 没错
-Yeah? -Yeah.
我这个是律师，还当义工
My guy is a lawyer,who does volunteer work.
而且他有这个东西
And he has one of these.
脸屁股？
A face ass?
下巴窝啦
A chin dimple.
我们这个是钱德的同事 人品好又聪明又会打扮
Well,you know,our guy works with Chandler.He's really nice and smart,and he's a great dresser.
你们看过他的身体吗？
-Have you seen your guy's body?
没有，他只有一颗飘来飘去的头
-No. Our guy's just a floating head.
我这个的身材很赞 他是我的客人
Well,my guy is spectacular. He's a massage client.
有一次他在按摩台上 就被我看光光了
And one time,when he was on the table,I looked at it. And I mean all of it.
你不能偷看 警察又不会抓
-You're not supposed to look. -Like there are police for that.
你会偷看？我被你按摩过   没错
You look? You massaged me.I know.
好，你那个或许身材很好 但我们这个很风趣
Fine. Your guy may have a great body,but our guy is really funny.
钱德式的风趣？
Chandler funny?
我们这个舞功高强 我这个饱读诗书
-Our guy's a great dancer. -My guy's well-read.
我们这个发质很好 我这个牙齿漂亮
-Our guy has great hair. -My guy has great teeth.
我们这个香得不得了
Our guy smells incredible.
你真这么迷恋他？
Do you want our guy to be your guy?
你的脸色不太好
Well,you don't look good,Joe.
冰箱坏了，我得把东西都吃掉
The fridge broke,so I had to eat everything.
冷盘、冰淇淋、莱姆…
Cold cuts,ice cream,limes.
咖啡色罐子里是什么？
What was in that brown jar?
那个还在？ 现在不在了
-That's still in there? -Not anymore.
总之你要怎么付钱给我？
So anyway,how do you want to pay me?
你要提供某种服务吗？
Is this a service you're providing me?
不是，是我要买冰箱 我们要买冰箱
No,for my new fridge. For our new fridge.
我们？我已经不住这里了
Our new fridge?I don't live here anymore.
那又怎样？ 听着，假设我们是离婚夫妻
-So what?Look,okay,suppose we were a divorced couple
我取得孩子的监护权
And I got custody of the kid. Right?
结果孩子死了 我总得买个新孩子
Now suppose the kid dies and I gotta buy a new kid.
好
Okay.
给我4百元
Give me $400!
幸好你很帅
Thank God,you're pretty.
盖勒教授
Professor Geller?
哦，是一名我不认识的学生
Oh,a student I don't know.
能不能跟您谈一下？
I was wondering if I could talk to you for a moment?
当然可以，是哪方面的事？
Yes,of course. What would this be regarding?
在你的研究室亲热
Making out in your office.
好，我们进去再说
Of course. Why don't we go inside.
怎么了？ 门把
-What? -Doorknob.
抱歉
Sorry.
我真的有事要讲 好，什么事？
I actually do need to talk to you.What about?
春假的事 春假的事？
-Spring vacation? -Spring vacation?
对，学校没课 很多人要去旅行…
Yeah,we have time off,and a lot of people are going on trips..
盖勒教授 是，菲森斯兰德教授…
-Professor Geller. -Yes,Professor Friesenstinlender.
我马上就好
I'll be with you in one moment.
那我就买一盒薄荷巧克力饼
So I will take one box of the Thin Mints.
你们不懂 伊丽莎白想找我跟她去旅行
You don't understand. Elizabeth was about to ask me to go on a trip with her.
这样叫慢慢来吗？
Is that taking it slow?
我还没准备好，我该怎么说？
-I'm not ready for this.What do I tell her?
实话实说，说你还没准备好
-Tell her the truth,tell her you're not ready.
可以试试
I could do that.
要是她不高兴呢？ 你就拿芭比娃娃逗她
-What if she gets upset? -Then you distract her with a Barbie doll.
或者你也可以…
Or you could just,you know,you...
你干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
我干什么？你弄坏我的冰箱
What the hell am I doing? You just broke my fridge!
什么？你怎么知道它坏了？
What? How do..?How do you know it's even broken?
它怎么坏的我会不知道吗？
You think I don't know what breaks my fridge?
你等一下
Excuse me!
看吧，坏了
Well,what do you know?Broken!
请赔4百
That'll be $400.
乔伊，我看见你推他了
Joey,I saw you push him.
是你推的
You pushed him.
乔伊，我没把它弄坏 它已经坏了一阵子了
Joey,I did not break this. Okay? That has been broken for a while.
我不是提过我们的冰箱的事？
Remember I told you about our fridge?
我还没拿到你该出的钱
I still haven't gotten the check for your half yet.
不要给他钱 你少插嘴，你撞坏我的冰箱
Do not give him any money!I'm not talking to you! You broke my fridge!
盖勒教授，你找我？ 是的，请进
-You wanted to see me,Professor Geller? -Yes. Please come in.
门把？ 对，你有点玩上瘾了
-Doorknob? -Yeah. It kind of grows on you.
我想继续上次春假的话题 好
I wanted to finish talking to you about spring vacation.Good.
听我说，我…
Look,I...
我跟你在一起很开心
Look,I'm having a great time with you.
我不想进展得太快 或是给我们太多压力
And I just don't want us to move too fast or put too much pressure on us.
所以很抱歉 我们还不能一起旅行，太快了
So I'm sorry,I just don't think we should go away together yet.It's too soon.
罗斯，你误会我的意思了
Ross,I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
我只是想告诉你 我要去佛罗里达2星期
I just wanted to tell you that I'm going to Florida for a couple weeks.
不，是你误会我的意思了
No.I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
我的意思是… 你好可爱
What I meant was..You are so adorable.
这个，我们来讨论这个
That. Let's talk about that.
你跟伊丽莎白谈得怎样？
-Hi. -Hi.How did it go with Elizabeth?
没事，只是一场误会
Fine. Just a misunderstanding.
她没有要找我去 她只是要告诉我她要去佛罗里达放春假
She didn't want me to go with her.She just wanted to let me know she's going to Florida for a spring vacation.
等等，她是去放春假 还是去春游？
Wait a minute. Is she going for spring vacation or spring break? Wahoo!
有什么差别？
What's the difference?
春假是跟爷爷奶奶共享天伦
Spring vacation,you're doing nice things with your grandparents.
春游是跟兄弟会的人上床
Spring break,you're doing frat guys.
并非每个人的春游都那样
You know what? Not all spring breaks are like that.
你做了什么？ 我跟我爸去埃及
-What did you do on yours? -I went to Egypt with my dad.
我可以想像 “看呐爸爸，是狮身人面像”
I can see it now. "Look,Dad,it's the Sphinx,wahoo!"
伊丽莎白那么正经 不会去“春游”
I think Elizabeth is a little more serious than: "Spring break,wahoo!"
好吗？她修了我的课
Come on,she's taking my class.
还跟教授上床 我去打给她
-And slept with the professor. -I'm gonna call her.
各位，这是赛巴斯钦
You guys,I want you to meet Sebastian.
我们刚刚在报摊认识 我们都买了《原野与河流》（著名的狩猎和钓鱼杂志）
We met at the newsstand. We both grabbed for the last Field and Stream.
怎么了，我一直在看啊
What? I read that.
你要咖啡吗？ 要，谢谢
-Can I get you a cup of coffee? -Yes. Thank you.
瑞秋，你这是什么意思？
-Rachel,what the hell is this?
什么？ 你叫我们帮你找人
-What?You ask us to find a guy,
却自己带了个人来
and you come traipsing in here with a guy of your own?
你们帮我找到人了？
You found me a guy?
对，我们在钱德的公司 相中一个可爱风趣的人
Yes. We found you a really cute,funny guy from Chandler's work.
我也找了一个不是怪胎的人
Yeah,and I found you one too,who is not a weirdo.
你们知道吗？真是谢谢你们 不过我带赛巴斯钦去就好了
You know what though,guys,I really appreciate that...but I'm gonna take Sebastian
你确定？我们这个很香喔
Are you sure? Our guy smells incredible.
别再提那个了好吗？
Would you stop it with that already?
你的咖啡
-Here you go. -Thank you.
赛巴斯钦，你有在当义工吗？
So,Sebastian,do you do any volunteer work?
没有，怎么了？
-Not really. Why?
没事，我只是认识一个 关心别人的单身汉
-No reason.I know a single guy who does care about other people.
你风趣吗？
Are you funny?
什么？ 你们在干什么？
-Excuse me? -What are you guys doing?
你风趣吗？讲个笑话来听
Are you funny? Tell us a joke!
我只是想和瑞秋喝杯咖啡
I just wanted to have coffee with Rachel.
很多人都想
Well,so do a lot of people.
说实话我该走了
-Actually,I gotta get going. -But you..
有空打电话给我 你没给我电话号码
-Give me a call sometime. -You didn't give me your phone number.
好，那就改天见
Okay,see you later.
原来他蛮风趣的
Turns out he is kind of funny.
你们太过份了 他人很好，却被你们赶走了
I cannot believe you guys!He was really nice,and he just left because of you!
赛巴斯钦耶？ 那是猫的名字吗？
Yeah,but "Sebastian"? What is that,a cat's name?
你知道我发现什么？ 他很容易被吓到
You know what I noticed,Rachel? He scares easy.
你想带这种人参加舞会吗？
Is that the kind of guy you wanna take to a ball?
“赛巴斯钦，要不要跳舞？”
"Hey,Sebastian,would you like to dance?"
“好，我得走了”
"Okay. I gotta go."
别再说了
Stop it.
瑞秋，对不起，我们太过份了
Rachel,we're very sorry.That is a very insensitive thing to do.
这样吧，让我们补偿你 我们有两个好男人让你挑
Let us make it up to you. We have two really great guys for you.
对啊，你有什么损失？ 搞不好会认识让你心动的人
Yeah,what have you got to lose?You might even end up with someone really special.
如果你选我这边的话
If you pick my guy.
好吧
-All right.
你愿意见我们找的人？ 我愿意
-So you will meet our guys?Yes
你要选谁都行，由你自己决定
It doesn't matter which one you choose. It's up to you.
我们这个很完美
Our guy is perfect.
或者你也可以选 菲比自己看不上眼的人
Or you could go out with the guy Phoebe deemed not good enough for herself.
菲比，你在这里 你弄坏我的冰箱，欠我4百
There you are! You broke my fridge.You owe me $400.
好吧 真的？
-Okay,sure. -Really?
技术上来说你欠我6百 你最近十次试镜我都有祈祷
Technically,you owe me $600 for sending out happy thoughts...on your last 10 auditions.
那就扯平了？
Call it even?
好吧
Okay.
回来了，伊丽莎白怎么说？
There you are.What did Elizabeth say?
她真的是要去德通纳春游
Turns out she is going to Daytona for "spring break,wahoo."
也就是有湿T恤美女选拔赛 男生朝女生身上扔水球
That means wet T-shirt contests,guys doing shots off of girls' bodies...
在陌生人身边醒来
waking up with strangers.
她会玩得很爽
She is gonna have a great time!
她要住可乐娜饭店吗？
Is she staying at the Hotel Corona?
你熟悉那里的饭店？ 当然，我参加过81年春游
-You know the hotels? -I was there! Spring Break '81,wahoo!
81年你才13岁
In 1981,you were 13.
那又怎样？我开车去卖T恤 玩得好开心
So? I drove down,sold T-shirts. Had a blast.
你们知道谁最会疯？ 酒醉的大学女生
You know who knows how to party? Drunk college chicks.
好，她不准去
Okay,she can't go.
罗斯，你不能叫她不要去 你们才交往没多久
You can't tell her not to go. You just started dating.
那我该怎么办？
-What am I supposed to do?
不怎么办，你只能接受
-You just have to be cool with it.
要是她跑去跟一堆人上床呢？
What if she goes down there and sleeps with a bunch of guys?
那这次你就别娶她
Well,maybe you don't marry this one.
对不起，这是很严肃的事
I'm sorry,this is very serious.
你知道吗？你喜欢她 她也喜欢你，不会有事的
And you know what,Ross?You like her,she likes you,everything's gonna be fine.
你说得对，我反应过度了
You're right. I'm probably overreacting.
她要住在滨海饭店 有大游泳池，每顿都有免费的饮料…
It's just she's staying at this party hotel on the beach...with a huge pool and free drinks with every meal.
她既然这么有钱 一定能赔偿她弄坏的冰箱
If she's got enough money for that,she can certainly pat for the fridge she broke.
你能去旅行真是好事 就是啊，我这学期那么用功
I'm so glad you're going on this trip.I've been working so hard this semester.
很需要疯狂一下，缓解压力 当然
I really need to go crazy,blow off some steam.Sure.
我不知道你的计划定了没
Look,I don't know if your plans are finalized yet,but...
还有一个办法可以缓解压力
I know a great way to blow off steam.
什么办法？ 你喜欢做手工艺吗？
-What? -Are you into crafts at all?
罗斯，你还好吗？
Ross,are you okay?
我当然很好 我只是在表示支持
Yeah. Of course I'm okay.I'm just being supportive.
支持你和这次旅行 还有这是什么？
Supportive of you and this whole trip...and what's this?
那是泳衣 你要穿它去见人？
It's a bathing suit?To wear in front of people?
这样叫支持吗？ 这样是吗？
Is that supportive?Is this?
太好了
Okay,good.
很高兴你答应见我们找的人 你一定会很喜欢他
-Hey. -Hi.We're so glad you decided to meet our guy. You'll like him so much.
你要什么时候见他？
-When do you want to meet him?
不晓得 我知道我明天不用加班
-I don't know.I don't work late tomorrow night.
明晚不错…
-Tomorrow night is good.
不过现在能做的事 为什么要拖到明天？
But why put off something till tomorrow that you could do it right now?
艾达，过来  什么
-Eldad,come here! -What?
艾达，这位是瑞秋 你好吗？
-This is Rachel. -How are you?
有点措手不及，不过我很好
A little blindsided but good.
艾达，坐…你坐过去
Eldad,sit down. Move over now.
这就对了
There you go. There you are.
好，我们知道了
Okay,we can take a hint!
你来干什么？ 这位是派屈克
What? What are you doing here?This is Patrick.
你来晚了 她跟我们那个在一起了
-Hi. -Hi.You're too late because she's already with our guy.
天哪，我是来晚了 他们正坐在沙发上聊天
You're right,I am too late. They're sitting on the couch and talking.
瑞秋 怎样？
Rachel?
这是派屈克
This is Patrick.
他就是我说的那个人
-Hi. -Hi.This is the guy I was telling you about.
相信我，这套西装 太委屈底下的身材了
This suit does not do justice to what's underneath it.
好，但是菲比 怎样？
Okay.But,Phoebe,
我现在有点事
I'm just sort of in the middle of something.
好，没关系，你坐
Okay. That's okay. Have a seat.
你不能这样
-You can't do that!
我走好了 坐下，我们占上风
-I should go.Sit down,we're winning.
也许我才应该走 不要，坐下
Maybe I should go.No. Have a seat!
瑞秋，你还没摸过艾达的头发
Rachel,you haven't touched Eldad's hair.
超柔顺的，你摸摸看 不必了
-He has the softest hair. Touch it. -I'm good.
瑞秋，派屈克很有钱 拿钱给她
Rachel,Patrick is really rich. Give her some money.
这个免费按摩的代价太高了
This isn't really worth the free massage.
没错，派屈克，再见
-That's right. Bye-bye. -No.
艾达配合多了，而且很会跳舞
Eldad is much more cooperative,and he can dance.
你跳舞给瑞秋看
You dance for Rachel.
不，拜托不要
Don't dance for me. Please!
你们是怎么搞的？
What is the matter with you?
没错，大家来说清楚 我…
Yeah,let's talk it out.
只有我觉得尴尬吗？
Am I the only one that this is embarrassing for?
我也有点尴尬
I'm a little embarrassed.
该尴尬的是你们 这实在是太不可理喻了
I'll tell you who should be embarrassed. It's you guys.
很谢谢你们 但我不需要你们帮我找人
I do not need you to get me a date.
那你为什么叫我们… 我还没说完
-Why did she ask us to..? -I am still talking!
你们还把我真正喜欢的人赶走
Then you chase away the one guy I actually liked.
我没有冒犯的意思，真的 恭喜你有那么多现金
No offense to you guys. Really,congratulations on...all the cash.
还有你…你的头发真的很柔顺
And you really do have very soft hair.
但我宁可自己参加晚会 也不要再受这种气，再见
But I'd much rather go to the ball by myself than go through any more of this.Goodbye.
你有用什么特别的润发乳吗？
Now,do you use some sort of special conditioner on that hair?
有，木瓜粹取液 谢谢
Papaya extract.Thank you.
好好去玩吧 我会的
So have a great time down there.-I will. -Yeah.
你有带那套泳衣吗？ 有
Did you pack that bathing suit? -Yeah.
我刚才把它藏起来 实在蛮好笑的
It was pretty funny when I hid it for a while.
总之…
Anyway.
我不是担心那套泳装太曝露 这一点我不在意
I am worried about that suit.Not because it's revealing,which I'm fine with.
我是关心你的健康，怕你晒到
I'm concerned about your health.Sun exposure.
放心，我带了一大堆防晒油 防晒系数30
Don't worry,I have plenty of sun block.-It's SPF 30. -All right.
如果真的有30就好了
Well,if what's in the bottle is actually 30.
有时候是30，有时候只有4 我发誓有很多都只是牛奶
Sometimes you get 30,sometimes it's 4 and...more often than not,it's just milk.
罗斯，你放心 我不是要去跟一堆男生鬼混
Ross,it's gonna be okay.I'm not going down there to hook up with a bunch of guys.
我很喜欢你 我喜欢我们的关系
I really like you.I like how things are going between us.
真的？ 对，我只是跟朋友们去玩一玩
-Really? -Yeah.I'm just going down there to relax and hang out with my friends.
好吧
Okay. Cool.
他们来了 伊丽莎白
Here they are!
打电话给我
Call me!
瑞秋，抱歉把那些人硬塞给你
Sorry for pushing those guys on you.
没关系，结果我玩得很开心
That's all right. I ended up having a really good time.
晚会很成功 筹到很多款，引起很多重视
The charity was a big success,and they raised a lot of money and awareness.
它是为什么筹款？
So,what was it for anyway?
我很想说是一种疾病
I wanna say a disease.
罗斯留了奇怪的留言 叫我们看MTV台
I just got this really weird message from Ross. He said to turn on MTV.
看，是伊丽莎白
Oh,my God,look! That's Elizabeth!
盖勒教授
Professor Geller.
回到13岁了 是啊
To be 13 again....